Guide to the Harry Gittelson collection, circa 1977-2007.
Gittelson, Harry collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harry Gittelson collection, circa 1977-2007.
7845
Harry. Gittelson
.4 cubic feet.
Photographs, ephemeral, audio recordings, printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes mementos of U.S. gay culture and politics, including Anita Bryant photograph and an autographed LP vinyl record album "Anita Bryant: Battle Hymn of the Republic", BAPA newsletter (1986-1988), directory (1987-1988), and letter of recognition to Mr. Gittelson (October 10, 1988), items related to Lilly Tomlin's character Edith Ann, Los Angeles Times December 20, 2003 obituary of Dr. Judd Marmor, Lalique statuette of a female figure, and a cake topper of 2 male figures bought in West Hollywood, May 2014.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell class of 1977. Vice President of the Los Angeles Business and Professional Association (BAPA) in the 1980s, he helped to develop membership as well as programing.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes mementos of U.S. gay culture and politics, including Anita Bryant photograph and an autographed LP vinyl record album "Anita Bryant: Battle Hymn of the Republic", BAPA newsletter (1986-1988), directory (1987-1988), and letter of recognition to Mr. Gittelson (October 10, 1988), items related to Lilly Tomlin's character Edith Ann, Los Angeles Times December 20, 2003 obituary of Dr. Judd Marmor, Lalique statuette of a female figure, and a cake topper of 2 male figures bought in West Hollywood, May 2014.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gittelson, Harry.; Bryant, Anita.; Marmor, Judd.
Subjects:
Gay couples.; Homosexuality.; Wedding cakes
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- The Normal Heart, 2014; DVD-2631 (Box 1)
- Edith Ann, 3 episodes, Undated; DVD-2632 (Box 1)
- Portrait, 1977-02-25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Taken at a press conference in Miami Beach, Florida
  Bryant, Anita
- Classroom resource kit on hate crimes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- BAPA newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- BAPA directory, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- BAPA recognition letter regarding President's Award, 1988-10-10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dr. Judd Marmor obituary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cake topper with 2 male figures, Undated; MU-1931 (Box 2)
- Lalique, 1990s statuette in original box, 1990; MU-1932 (Box 2)
- Edith Ann doll, Undated; MU-1933 (Box 2)
- "Anita Bryant sucks oranges" button, Undated; MU-1934 (Box 2)
- Battle hymn of the republic, 1973; SR-26423; Bryant, Anita
  Autographed
  Phonograph record